[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the study of winds.", "correct_answer": "anemology", "incorrect_answers": ["conilogy", "lithology", "campanology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Transformers 2, what kind of car is Sideswipe?", "correct_answer": "Chevrolet Corvette", "incorrect_answers": ["Lamborghini", "Audi R8", "Ferrari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Rick Chance daredevil hobby/sport?", "correct_answer": "Bungee(Base) Jumping", "incorrect_answers": ["Motorcycle riding", "Cock Fighting", "Jet-skiing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Bond movies does this phrase belong to Youre a rare challenge, Mr. Bond.?", "correct_answer": "Die Another Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Thunderball", "None of these", "Casino Royale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mix 1 ts powdered sugar and 2 ts water with some crushed ice into a glass. Then add 2 1/2 oz bourbon whiskey and some mint sprigs on top. \nYou should leave it until the glass is frosted.", "correct_answer": "Mint Julep", "incorrect_answers": ["Pina Colada", "Margarita", "Froot Loop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the poem, In The Naked Bed, In Platos Cave", "correct_answer": "Delmore Schwartz", "incorrect_answers": ["Allen Ginsberg", "Thilios Parmedes", "Langston Hughes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following astronauts was not among the first human beings to orbit the moon?", "correct_answer": "John Young", "incorrect_answers": ["James Lovell", "Frank Borman", "William Anders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is generally accepted that the name of these islands of volcanic origin derives from a Latin term, meaning Island of the Dogs.", "correct_answer": "The Canary Islands", "incorrect_answers": ["The Galapagos Islands", "Corn Islands", "The Solentiname Islands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Willy Wonka decide to become a candy maker according to the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "Because his father forbade him to eat candy", "incorrect_answers": ["Because he was obese as a child and was not allowed to eat candy", "Because he loved the smell of chocolate", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these Spielberg movies was not released in the 1980s?", "correct_answer": "1941", "incorrect_answers": ["Always", "Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "Raiders of the Lost Ark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these rivers is longest?", "correct_answer": "Huang", "incorrect_answers": ["Lena", "Amur", "Ob-Irtysh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Lando make a threatening move toward Han Solo in Star Wars: Episode 5?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]